ineedmotivation.com 2007-06-16

# Privacy Policy - INeedMotivation.com

  | **INeedMotivation.com's Privacy Policy**  
---|---  
  
**The web site you have entered is operated by INeedMotivation.com  
_Last updated: January 3rd 2006_

Introduction

**   
INeedMotivation.com want to help you make the most of your visit to our web site, and that includes helping to protect your personal privacy. Most of the features on our web site are offered without collecting any Personal Information from you. You can surf our site and view much of our content anonymously. For those areas of our web site and services that do require us to collect Personal Information, this Privacy Policy will tell you what you need to know to make good decisions for yourself and your family.

This Privacy Policy discloses when and how we collect, use, share, and safeguard information from this web site. The Personal Information we collect depends on what you do when you visit our site or use the various products or services we offer. This Privacy Policy also explains what to do if you do not want to provide Personal Information when you visit our web site, and how to correct or change information you have already provided to us.

By using this web site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as posted in this area of the site. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use our web site.

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means personally identifiable information, such as your name, street address, telephone number, and e-mail address. When Personal Information is collected, you will know because you will have to fill out a form on the web site. When you make a purchase, or sign up for a paid service, we will also collect your credit card information as additional Personal Information. We will use credit card information only to complete the transactions you have requested. 

**Collection of Personal Information**   
INeedMotivation.com collects Personal Information from visitors to our web site in the following ways: 

\- Subscriptions to our free daily, weekly, and monthly newsletters, which include updates, special offers and promotions from INeedMotivation.com.  
\- Purchases of merchandise (including course downloads), Streaming audio and video courses & seminars, personal & business coaching, and transactions where home delivery is required.   
\- E-mail transmitted via various links on our web sites.

The use of any of these services is entirely optional and voluntary; however, if you do not provide the Personal Information requested, we may elect to not make the related services available for your use. If you send us an e-mail in which you disclose Personal Information, we will use it to discuss the subject of your correspondence and, if appropriate, share it with other parties (such as merchant processor of your payment like Paypal or 2Checkout). 

If you send us an e-mail, you should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. So, if your communication needs to include sensitive information like your bank account, credit card, or social security number, please contact us by postal mail or telephone (See Contact Us Page) rather than e-mail. 

**Cookies**

INeedMotivation.com uses [www.opentracker.net](http://www.opentracker.net/) to collect and analyze traffic on our site. This information helps us understand customer interests and helps us improve our website. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. Opentracker does not sell, give, or trade the statistics they store to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes.

In order to track your use of the site, "cookies" may be employed. Cookies are pieces of information that are sent by web sites and stored in your computer's hard drive, which provide you a service by allowing us to recognize your computer to save you from having to re-enter the same data every time you visit our web sites. They also allow us to learn how visitors use our web site. This user data is aggregated for tracking purposes primarily by tallying pages viewed throughout our web sites and logging Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses and browser types.

Aggregated usage data enables us to tailor our content to our visitors’ interests. This information does not reveal your identity although, in some cases, we may have to combine this non-identifiable information with Personal Information to protect our service, web site, visitors or others.

If you do not want to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject them. However, if you turn cookies off, you may have problems using some features and services on our site. 

**Visitors From Outside the United States & Canada**  
All Personal Information collected at our web site is collected and stored in the United States as well as in Canada. By submitting Personal Information to this web site, you are consenting to the storage of your Personal Information in the United States, as well as in Canada.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We limit the manner in which your Personal Information is used. We use Personal Information to provide you the products and services you want, to better understand and serve the needs of the INeedMotivation.com community, and to provide news and information to community members on new content, products and features of the web site via direct e-mail. If you have registered with us and do not want to be contacted in the future by INeedMotivation.com, please contact us to "Opt Out".

Finally, please note that we will release your Personal Information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order. 

**Links to Third Party Web Sites**  
Please be advised that this web site contains certain hyperlinks to other web sites, some of which may display INeedMotivation.com's logos and content. These web sites may have privacy policies; however, all of these web sites and their privacy policies are independent of our web sites or this Privacy Policy. INeedMotivation.com is not responsible for compliance with other web sites’ privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing any Personal Information to these web sites. 

**Limitations on Use of Personal Information**  
We will only use or retain your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy, and only for so long as is needed to fulfill your requests, support the services you have requested, process your orders, or comply with the law.

**Security of Personal Information**   
We take reasonable precautions to keep your Personal Information secure, including the use of Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology to protect credit card information and other Personal Information you provide in connection with purchases, paid subscriptions or other similar transactions. 

**Access/ Correct/ Update Personal Information**  
If you would like to know what Personal Information INeedMotivation.com has concerning you, send an e-mail via our contact us page. We will contact you by mail to verify your identity and provide you the information you request. If you would like to correct or update your Personal Information, including providing a new e-mail address, send an e-mail via our contact us page. Please be sure to include your old e-mail address. 

**Changes in This Privacy Policy**   
INeedMotivation.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here and we will change the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed. Contact us If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy.
